|     |     |
| --- | --- |

|     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **You are 1 of 875 active visitors** | **Saturday, October 26, 2024** |

**EMAIL NEWS**

Main Email List:

Subscribe  
Unsubscribe

State Email Lists:  

**SUPPORT KABA****�** [Join/Renew Online](http://keepandbeararms.com/custaccount/default.asp)  
**�** [Join/Renew by Mail](http://keepandbeararms.com/members/mail.htm)  
**�** [Make a Donation](http://keepandbeararms.com/donations/)  
**�** [Magazine Subscriptions](http://keepandbeararms.com/Magazines/default.asp)  
**�** [KABA Memorial Fund](http://keepandbeararms.com/MemorialFund/)  
**�** [Advertise Here](http://keepandbeararms.com/about/advertise.asp)  
**�** [Use KABA Free Email](http://keepandbeararms.com/webservices/freemail/default.asp)  

**� [JOIN/Renew NOW!](http://keepandbeararms.com/custaccount/Default.asp) �** **SUPPORT OUR SUPPORTERS**  

**YOUR VOTE COUNTS**

|     |
| --- |
| Do you oppose Biden's anti-gun executive orders?  <br>Yes  <br>No  <br>Undecided |
| [Current results](http://keepandbeararms.com/polls/pollmentorres.asp)  <br>[Earlier poll results](http://keepandbeararms.com/polls/pollmentorhist.asp)4773 people voted |

**SPONSORED LINKS**

 **»** [U.S. Gun Laws](http://gunla.ws/qgml)  
**»** [AmeriPAC](http://www.ameripac.org/)  
**»** [NoInternetTax](http://www.nointernettax.org/)  
**»** [Gun Show On The Net](http://www.gunshowonthenet.com/)  
**»** [2nd Amendment Show](http://www.2ndamendmentshow.com/)  
**»** [SEMPER FIrearms](http://www.semperfirearms.com/)  
**»** [Colt Collectors Assoc.](http://coltcollectors.org/)  
**»** [Personal Defense Solutions](http://www.personaldefensesolutions.net/) 

KeepAndBearArms.com Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

**Last Updated:** May 28, 2009

KeepAndBearArms.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to Privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.  We are committed to providing improvements in the below policy if warranted.

By accessing or using the KeepAndBearArms.com web site, you agree to the terms of the KeepAndBearArms.com Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. KeepAndBearArms.com reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or entering contests, KeepAndBearArms.com may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, KeepAndBearArms.com may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. In the process of administering our site, we maintain and track usage through Web server logs. Web server logs provide such information as what types of browsers are accessing our site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our servers experience significant load. We use this information to improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is not used to personally identify you.

**Your Personal Information**

KeepAndBearArms.com collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about special offers and other products and services of KeepAndBearArms.com and selected third parties.

**Share Your Personal Information**

We will not sell, rent or lease to others telephone numbers or e-mail addresses. We will share the personal data you provide only with other KeepAndBearArms.com entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above, except as provided below (see Consent).

**Consent**

KeepAndBearArms.com will use and share the personally identifiable information you provided to us in ways related to those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

**Reprinting personal information**

Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, is available to all persons accessing that site.

**Privacy related concerns**

Should you have questions or concerns relating to this Privacy Statement or compliance with it, please use the following form to contact us:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Email:** |     |
| **Subject:** |     |
| **Comment:** |     |
|     |     |
|     |     |    

 **QUOTES TO REMEMBER**"Some people think that the Second Amendment is an outdated relic of an earlier time. Doubtless some also think that constitutional protections of other rights are outdated relics of earlier times. We The People own those rights regardless, unless and until We The People repeal them. For those who believe it to be outdated, the Second Amendment provides a good test of whether their allegiance is really to the Constitution of the United States, or only to their preferences in public policies and audiences. The Constitution is law, not vague aspirations, and we are obligated to protect, defend, and apply it. If the Second Amendment were truly an outdated relic, the Constitution provides a method for repeal. The Constitution does not furnish the federal courts with an eraser." --9th Circuit Court Judge Andrew Kleinfeld, dissenting opinion in which the court refused to rehear the case while citing deeply flawed anti-Second Amendment nonsense (Nordyke v. King; opinion filed April 5, 2004)

**COPYRIGHT POLICY:** The posting of copyrighted articles and other content, in whole or in part, is not allowed here. We have made an effort to educate our users about this policy and we are extremely serious about this. Users who are caught violating this rule will be warned and/or banned.  
If you are the owner of content that you believe has been posted on this site without your permission, [please contact our webmaster by following this link](http://keepandbeararms.com/about/contact_us.asp). Please include with your message: (1) the particulars of the infringement, including a description of the content, (2) a link to that content here and (3) information concerning where the content in question was originally posted/published. We will address your complaint as quickly as possible. Thank you.

 **NOTICE:**  The information contained in this site is not to be considered as legal advice. In no way are Keep And Bear Arms .com or any of its agents responsible for the actions of our members or site visitors. Also, because this web site is a Free Speech Zone, opinions, ideas, beliefs, suggestions, practices and concepts throughout this site may or may not represent those of Keep And Bear Arms .com. All rights reserved. Articles that are original to this site may be redistributed provided they are left intact and a link to [http://www.KeepAndBearArms.com](http://www.keepandbeararms.com/) is given. [Click here for Contact Information](http://keepandbeararms.com/about/contact_us.asp) for representatives of KeepAndBearArms.com.

[Thawte.com](http://www.thawte.com/) is the leading provider of Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) and digital certificate solutions used by enterprises, Web sites, and consumers to conduct secure communications and transactions over the Internet and private networks.

KeepAndBearArms.com, Inc. © 1999-2024, All Rights Reserved. [Privacy Policy](http://keepandbeararms.com/about/privacy_policy.asp)
